British Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
British Painting Photograph Collection
1900-2005
VRC 17
Yale University Arts Library
37
89 boxes
Collection consists of mounted black and white and color reproductions of British paintings. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of mounted black and white and color reproductions of British paintings. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged alphabetically by individual artist name. The individual artist material is further divided primarily by the location of the work. The individual artist portion is preceded by a grouping arranged chronologically and sub-arranged by location.
Painting, British; Photographs; Reproductions
- Britain (Box 1)
  General
  (5,576 photographs)
  - General (Box 1)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 1)
      Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings
    - 16th century (Box 1)
  - Drawings (1 photograph) (Box 1)
  - Paintings (Box 1)
    (5,542 photographs)
    - 13th century (3 photographs) (Box 1)
    - 14th century (11 photographs) (Box 1)
      Xx for Wilton Diptych see Painting France, 14th century, also Large size Painting France
    - 15th century (7 photographs) (Box 1)
    - 16th century (32 photographs) (Box 1)
      Xx for The Ditchley Portrait of Queen Elizabeth I, see Painting Flanders, Gheeraerts, Marcus the younger
    - 17th century (13 photographs) (Box 2)
    - 18th century (19 photographs) (Box 2)
    - 19th – 20th century (6 photographs) (Box 2)
      - Artist Unknown (Box 2)
      - A (88 photographs) (Box 3)
        - Individual Artists (22 photographs) (Box 3)
          - Allan, David, 1744-1796 (6 photographs) (Box 3)
          - Alma-Tadema, Lawrence, 1836-1912 (Box 3)
            - Various Titles (1 photograph) (Box 3)
            - Private Collection (10 photographs) (Box 3)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (40 photographs) (Box 3)
          - Ansdell, Richard, 1815-1885 (4 photographs) (Box 4)
          - Auerbach, Frank, 1931- (5 photographs) (Box 4)
        - B (625 photographs) (Box 4)
          - Individual Artists (Box 4)
          - Ba (25 photographs) (Box 4)
          - Be-Bo (22 photographs) (Box 4)
          - Br-By (25 photographs) (Box 4)
          - Bacon, Francis, 1909-1992 (Box 5)
            - Location Unknown (25 photographs) (Box 5)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (25 photographs) (Box 5)
            - London (20 photographs) (Box 5)
            - New York (21 photographs) (Box 5)
          - Barry, James, 1741-1806 (20 photographs) (Box 6)
            XxPrints Britain
          - Beardsley, Aubrey, 1872-1898 (7 photographs) (Box 6)
          - Beechey, William, 1753-1839 (19 photographs) (Box 6)
          - Beerbohm, Max, 1872-1956 (11 photographs) (Box 6)
          - Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961 (5 photographs) (Box 6)
          - Blake, William, 1757-1827 (Box 7)
            Xx Prints Britain
            - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 7)
              - Various Titles (33 photographs) (Box 7)
              - Heads of the Poets (11 photographs) (Box 7)
              - Illustrations (Box 7)
                - Dante (21 photographs) (Box 7)
                - Milton (14 photographs) (Box 8)
                - The New Testament (29 photographs) (Box 8)
          - Bomberg, David, 1890-1958 (4 photographs) (Box 9)
          - Bone, David M., 1876-1953 (9 photographs) (Box 9)
          - Bonington, Richard Parkes, 1801-1828 (29 photographs) (Box 9)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (25 photographs) (Box 9)
              - London (53 photographs) (Box 10)
          - Boughton, George Henry, 1833-1905 (9 photographs) (Box 10)
          - Brangwyn, Frank, 1867-1906 (40 photographs) (Box 11)
            Includes two folders of miscellaneous clippings
          - Brockhurst, Gerald, 1890- (4 photographs) (Box 11)
          - Brooking, Charles, 1723-1759 (5 photographs) (Box 11)
          - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893 (32 photographs) (Box 12)
          - Browne, Haflot ("Phiz"), 1815-1882 (4 photographs) (Box 12)
          - Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898 (Box 12)
            - Drawings (25 photographs) (Box 12)
            - Paintings (Box 12)
              - Location Unknown (25 photographs) (Box 12)
              - Miscellaneous Cities (26 photographs) (Box 13)
              - London (22 photographs) (Box 13)
        - C (445 photographs) (Box 13)
          - Individual Artists (Box 13)
          - Ca-Ch (18 photographs) (Box 13)
          - Co-Cu (30 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Cadell, Francis Campbell Boileau, 1883-1937 (6 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Calvert, Edward, 1799-1883 (5 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Cameron, D.Y. (3 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Catherwood, Frederick, 1799-1854 (8 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Chinnery, George, 1774-1852 (7 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Clausen, George, 1852-1944 (10 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Conder, Charles, 1868-1909 (4 photographs) (Box 14)
          - Constable, John, 1776-1837 (Box 15)
            - Location Unknown (52 photographs) (Box 15)
            - Private Collections (12 photographs) (Box 15)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (56 photographs) (Box 16)
            - London (10 photographs) (Box 17)
              - National Gallery (18 photographs) (Box 17)
              - Tate Gallery (21 photographs) (Box 17)
              - Victoria and Albert Museum (21 photographs) (Box 17)
            - New York (12 photographs) (Box 17)
          - Cooper, Samuel, 1609-1672 (8 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cosway, Richard, 1742-1821 (5 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cotes, Francis, 1725-1770 (24 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cotman, John Sell, 1782-1842 (26 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cowper, Frank Cadogan, 1877-1958 (4 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cox, David, 1783-1859 (8 photographs) (Box 18)
          - Cozens, Alexander, 1752-1797 (6 photographs) (Box 19)
          - Cozens, John Robert, 1717-1786 (25 photographs) (Box 19)
          - Crane, Walter, 1845-1915 (8 photographs) (Box 19)
          - Crome, John, 1769-1821 (32 photographs) (Box 19)
          - Cruikshank, George, 1792-1878 (6 photographs) (Box 19)
        - D (147 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Individual Artists (33 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Dadd, Richard, 1819-1887 (11 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Danby, Francis, 1793-1861 (10 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Dance, Nathaniel, 1734-1811 (11 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Daniell, Thomas, 1749-1840 (16 photographs) (Box 20)
          - Davie, Alan, 1920- (11 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Devis, Arthur, 1711-1787 (18 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Devis, Arthur William, 1763-1822 (18 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Dobson, William, Sir, 1610-1646 (4 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Dulac, Edmund, 1862- (2 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Dunlop, R.O., 1894- (3 photographs) (Box 21)
          - Dyce, William, 1806-1864 (10 photographs) (Box 21)
        - E (53 photographs) (Box 22)
          - Individual Artists (4 photographs) (Box 22)
          - Eardley, Joan, 1921-1963 (6 photographs) (Box 22)
          - Egg, Augustus, 1816-1863 (5 photographs) (Box 22)
          - Etty, William, Sir, 1787-1849 (15 photographs) (Box 22)
            - London (12 photographs) (Box 22)
            - Manchester (5 photographs) (Box 22)
            - Oxford (6 photographs) (Box 22)
        - F (148 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Individual Artists (18 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Faed, Thomas, 1826-1900 (5 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Ferneley, John, 1782-1860 (13 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Fildes, Luke, 1844-1927 (5 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Flaxman, John, 1755-1826 (5 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Flint, William H., 1880-1969 (16 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Foster, Myles Birket, 1825-1899 (7 photographs) (Box 23)
          - Frampton, Reginald, 1872-1923 (4 photographs) (Box 24)
          - Freud, Lucian, 1922- (13 photographs) (Box 24)
          - Frith, William Powell, 1819-1909 (18 photographs) (Box 24)
          - Furse, Charles Wellington, 1868-1904 (3 photographs) (Box 24)
          - Fuseli, Henry, 1741-1825 (Box 24)
            - Drawings (16 photographs) (Box 24)
            - Paintings (25 photographs) (Box 24)
        - G (442 photographs) (Box 25)
          - Individual Artists (Box 25)
          - Ga-Gi (18 photographs) (Box 25)
          - Gi-Gz (13 photographs) (Box 25)
          - Gainsborough, Thomas, 1727-1788 (Box 26)
            - Drawings (31 photographs) (Box 26)
            - Paintings (Box 27–28)
              - Locations Unknown (134 photographs) (Box 28)
              - Private collections (19 photographs) (Box 29)
              - Miscellaneous cities (45 photographs) (Box 29)
              - London (21 photographs) (Box 30)
                - National Gallery (34 photographs) (Box 30)
                - Tate Gallery (10 photographs) (Box 30)
              - New York (18 photographs) (Box 31)
              - Philadelphia (7 photographs) (Box 31)
              - Washington, D.C. (13 photographs) (Box 31)
          - Geddes, Andrew, 1783-1844 (3 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Gilbert and George (8 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Gill, Colin, 1892- (3 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Gilman, Harold, 1876-1919 (7 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Gilpin, Sawrey, 1733-1807 (7 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Girtin, Thomas, 1775-1802 (22 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Godward, John William, 1861-1922 (5 photographs) (Box 32)
          - Godward, John William, 1861-1922 (33 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Gore, Spencer, 1878-1914 (8 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Grant, Duncan, 1885- (13 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Greenaway, Kate, 1845-1901 (4 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Grimshaw, John Atkinson, 1836-1893 (6 photographs) (Box 33)
        - H (468 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Individual Artists (13 photographs) (Box 33)
          - Ha (24 photographs) (Box 33)
          - He-Hi (19 photographs) (Box 34)
          - Ho (27 photographs) (Box 34)
          - Hu (7 photographs) (Box 34)
          - Hamilton, Gavin, 1730-1797 (6 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Harlow, George Henry, 1787-1819 (9 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Hayman, Francis, 1708-1776 (9 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Haytley, Edward, active 1746-1761 (3 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Herring, John Frederick, 1795-1865 (14 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Highmore, Joseph, 1692-1780 (8 photographs) (Box 35)
          - Hilliard, Nicolas, 1547-1619 (10 photographs) (Box 36)
          - Hockney, David, 1937- (30 photographs) (Box 36)
          - Hodges, William, 1744-1797 (6 photographs) (Box 36)
          - Hodgkins Frances, 1870-1947 (7 photographs) (Box 36)
          - Hogarth, William, 1697-1 (Box 37)
            - Drawings (8 photographs) (Box 37)
            - Paintings (Box 37)
              - Unknown collections (13 photographs) (Box 37)
              - Miscellaneous cities, A-Z (23 photographs) (Box 37)
                - London (Box 38)
                - Miscellaneous locations (13 photographs) (Box 38)
                - National Gallery (26 photographs) (Box 38)
                - John Soane's Museum (15 photographs) (Box 38)
                - Tate Gallery (34 photographs) (Box 39)
          - Holland, James, 1800-1870 (4 photgraphs) (Box 40)
          - Hone, Nathaniel, 1718-1784 (4 photographs) (Box 40)
          - Hoppner, John, 1758-1810 (Box 40)
            - Unknown collections (44 photographs) (Box 40–41)
            - Private collections (10 photographs) (Box 41)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (20 photographs) (Box 41)
          - Hudson, Thomas, 1701-1779 (13 photographs) (Box 41)
          - Huggins, William, 1820-1884 (5 photographs) (Box 42)
          - Hughes, Arthur, 1832-1915 (17 photographs) (Box 42)
          - Hunt, William Holman, 1827-1910 (27 photographs) (Box 42)
        - I – J (90 photographs) (Box 42)
          - Individual Artists (23 photographs) (Box 42)
          - Ibbetson, Julius Caesar, 1759-1817 (3 photographs) (Box 43)
          - John, Augustus, 1878-1934 (Box 43)
            - Drawings (5 photographs) (Box 43)
            - Paintings (45 photographs) (Box 43)
          - John, Gwendolyn, 1876-1939 (9 photographs) (Box 43)
          - Juta, Jan, act.1934- (5 photographs) (Box 43)
        - K (136 photographs) (Box 44)
          - Individual Artists (12 photographs) (Box 44)
          - Kaufmann, Angelica, 1741-1807 (22 photographs) (Box 44)
          - Kitaj, Ronald, 1932- (14 photographs) (Box 44)
          - Kneller, Godfrey, 1646-1723 (Box 44)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (15 photographs) (Box 44)
            - London (Box 45)
              - National Portrait Gallery (45 photographs) (Box 45)
          - Knight, Harold, 1874-1961 (Box 46)
          - Knight, Laura, 1877-1970 (15 photographs) (Box 46)
          - Knight, Loxton, 1905- (4 photographs) (Box 46)
        - L (341 photographs) (Box 46)
          - La (14 photographs) (Box 46)
          - Le-Lz (18 photographs) (Box 46)
          - Lamb, Henry, 1885- (9 photographs) (Box 47)
          - Landseer, Edwin, Sir, 1802-1873 (Box 47)
            - Miscellaneous cities, A-Z (19 photographs) (Box 47)
            - London (15 photographs0 (Box 47)
          - Larkin, William, active 1610-1620 (5 photographs) (Box 47)
          - Laszio, Philipp Alexius de (19 photographs) (Box 47)
          - Lavery, John, 1856-1941 (30 photographs) (Box 48)
          - Lawrence, Thomas, Sir, 1769-1830 (Box 49)
            - Location Unknown (12 photographs) (Box 49)
            - Private collections (Box 49)
            - Miscellaneous cities, A-Z Box 50 (Box 50)
            - London (18 photographs) (Box 50)
            - New York (9 photogrpahs) (Box 50)
          - Lear, Edward, 1812-1888 (18 photographs) (Box 50)
          - Leighton, Frederick, Sir, 1830-1896 (30 photographs) (Box 51)
          - Lely, Peter, Sir, 1618-1680 (Box 51)
            - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 51)
            - Paintings (36 photographs) (Box 51)
          - Lewis, John Frederick, 1805-1876 (14 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Lewis, Wyndham, 1884-1957 (4 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Linnell, John, 1792-1882 (8 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Loutherbourg, Philippe Jacques de, 1740-1812 (8 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Lowry, Lawrence S., 1887- (13 photographs) (Box 52)
        - M (305 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Ma-Md (25 photographs) (Box 52)
          - Me-Mz (26 photographs) (Box 53)
          - Mackintosh, Charles Rennie, 1868-1928 (11 photographs) (Box 53)
          - Maclise, Daniel, 1806-1870 (10 photographs) (Box 53)
          - MacTaggart, William, 1835-1910 (7 photographs) (Box 53)
          - Marshall, Benjamin, 1767-1833 (18 photographs) (Box 53)
          - Martin, John, 1789-1854 (30 photographs) (Box 53)
          - Millais, John Everett, 1829-1896 (Box 54)
            - Miscellaneous cities, A-Z (55 photographs) (Box 54)
            - London (14 photographs) (Box 54)
          - Moore, Albert, 1841-1893 (10 photographs) (Box 54)
          - Moore, Henry S., 1898-1986 (39 photographs) (Box 55)
          - Morland, George, 1763-1804 (28 photographs) (Box 55)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (14 photographs) (Box 55)
          - Morley, Harry, 1881- (7 photographs) (Box 56)
          - Morley, Harry, 1881- (8 photographs) (Box 56)
          - Mulready, William, 1786-1863 (12 photographs) (Box 56)
          - Munnings, Alfred, Sir, 1878-1959 (21 photographs) (Box 56)
        - N (118 photographs) (Box 56)
          - Individual Artists (16 photographs) (Box 56)
          - Nash, Paul, 1889-1946 (6 photographs) (Box 57)
            - Private Collection (15 photographs) (Box 57)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (14 photographs) (Box 57)
          - Nasmyth, Alexander, 1758-1840 (4 photographs) (Box 57)
          - Nebot, Balthasar, act. Ca. 1730-1762 (5 photographs) (Box 57)
          - Nicholson, Ben, 1894-1942 (Box 57)
            - Unknown Collection (20 photographs) (Box 57)
            - Private Collection (29 photographs) (Box 58)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (9 photographs) (Box 58)
        - O (61 photographs) (Box 58)
          - Individual Artists (8 photographs) (Box 58)
          - Oliver, Issac, 1556-1617 (5 photographs) (Box 58)
          - Opie, John, 1761-1807 (19 photographs) (Box 58)
          - Orchardson, William Quiller, 1832-1910 (3 photographs) (Box 59)
          - Orpen, William, 1878-1937 (29 photographs) (Box 59)
        - P (139 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Pa (13 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Pe-Pi (17 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Po-Py (13 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Palmer, Samuel, 1805-1881 (Box 60)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (20 photographs) (Box 60)
            - London (8 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Pasmore, Victor, 1908- (10 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Paton, Joseph Noel, 1821-1901 (5 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Peploe, Samuel John, 1871-1934 (4 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Peters, Matthew W., 1742-1841 (4 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Pettie, John, 1839-1893 (5 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Philpot, Glyn Warren, 1884-1937 (5 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Piper, John, 1903- (25 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Pollard, James, 1792-1867 (5 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Poynter, Edward (6 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Procter, Ernest (3 photographs) (Box 61)
          - Prout, Samuel, 1783-1852 (8 photoggraphs) (Box 61)
        - R (856 photographs) (Box 62)
          - Ra-Re (11 photographs) (Box 62)
          - Ri (25 photographs) (Box 62)
          - Ro-Ry (11 photographs) (Box 62)
          - Raeburn, Henry, Sir, 1756-1823 (39 photographs) (Box 63)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (21 photographs) (Box 64)
            - Edinburgh (15 photographs) (Box 64)
            - London (9 photographs) (Box 64)
            - New York (7 photographs) (Box 64)
          - Ramsay, Allen, 1713-1784 (22 photographs) (Box 64)
          - Reynolds, Joshua, Sir, 1723-1792 (Box 65-66-67)
            - Location Unknown (145 photographs) (Box 65-66-67)
            - Private Collections (48 photographs) (Box 68)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 69)
              - Cities A-L (17 photographs) (Box 69)
              - Cities M-Z (19 photographs) (Box 69)
            - London (31 photographs) (Box 69)
              - Tate Gallery (19 photographs) (Box 69)
              - Wallace Collection (18 photographs) (Box 70)
            - New York (12 photographs) (Box 70)
            - Washington, D.C. (7 photographs) (Box 70)
          - Richardson, Jonathan, 1665-1745 (9 photographs) (Box 70)
          - Richter, H.D., 1874- (3 photographs) (Box 70)
          - Ricketts, Charles, de, 1866-1931 (5 photographs) (Box 70)
          - Roberts, David, 1796-1864 (9 photographs) (Box 70)
          - Romney, George, 1734-1802 (60 photographs) (Box 71)
            - Private Collections (12 photographs) (Box 72)
            - Miscellaneous cities, A-Z (16 photographs) (Box 72)
            - London (14 photographs) (Box 72)
            - New Haven (9 photographs) (Box 72)
            - New York (12 photographs) (Box 72)
            - Philadelphia (10 photographs) (Box 72)
            - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 72)
          - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882 (Box 73)
            - Drawings (20 photographs) (Box 73)
            - Paintings (Box 73)
              - Miscellaneous media, locations, and titles (15 photographs) (Box 73)
              - Miscellaneous Cities (18 photographs) (Box 73)
              - London (28 photographs) (Box 73)
          - Rothenstein, William (4 photographs) (Box 73)
          - Rowlandson, Thomas, 1756-1826 (Box 74)
            - Drawings (53 photographs) (Box 74)
            - Paintings (31 photographs) (Box 74)
          - Runciman, Alexander, 1736-1785 (12 photographs) (Box 75)
          - Runciman, John, 1744-1768 (6 photographs) (Box 75)
          - Ruskin, John (18 photographs) (Box 75)
          - Russell, John, 1745-1806 (11 photographs) (Box 75)
        - S (348 photographs) (Box 76)
          - Sa-Sk (34 photographs) (Box 76)
          - Sm-Sp (24 photographs) (Box 76)
          - St-Sw (24 photographs) (Box 76)
          - Sandby, Paul, 1725-1809 ( 22 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Sandby, Thomas, 1721-1798 (5 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Scott, David, 1806-1849 (5 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Scott, Samuel, 1703-1772 (15 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Seymour, James, 1702-1752 (5 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Shannon, Charles, 1863-1937 (6 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Shayer, William, 1788-1879 (7 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Shee, Martin Archer, Sir, 1769-1850 (5 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Sheringham, George, 1884- (7 photographs) (Box 77)
          - Sickert, Walter Richard, 1860-1942 (40 photogrpahs) (Box 78)
          - Sims, Charles, 1873-1928 (4 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Singleton, Henry, 1766-1839 (4 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Spencer, Stanley, Sir, 1891-1954 (27 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Squirrel, L.R., 1893- (5 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Stevens, Alfred, 1817-1875 (5 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Strudwick, John Melhuish, 1849-1918 (5 photographs) (Box 78)
          - Stubbs, George, 1724-1806 (Box 79)
            - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 79)
            - Paintings (61 photographs) (Box 79)
          - Sutherland, Graham, 1903-1980 (32 photographs) (Box 80)
        - T (378 photographs) (Box 80)
          - Individual Artists (11 photographs) (Box 80)
          - Thornhill, James, 1675-1734 (6 photographs) (Box 80)
          - Towne, Charles, 1763-1840 (2 photographs) (Box 80)
          - Turner, Joseph Mallord William, 1775-1851 (Box 81)
            - Drawings (12 photographs) (Box 81)
            - Watercolors (66 photographs) (Box 81)
              - Miscellaneous Cities Box (16 photographs) (Box 82)
                - London (10 photographs) (Box 82)
                - British Museum (25 photographs) (Box 82)
            - Paintings (Box 82)
              - Various titles (33 photographs) (Box 82)
              - Private Collections (7 photographs) (Box 82)
              - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 83)
                - Cities A-C (16 photographs) (Box 83)
                - Cities O-Z (28 photographs) (Box 83)
                - London (Box 83)
                - Miscellaneous media, locations, and titles (6 photographs) (Box 83)
                - National Gallery (33 photographs) (Box 83)
                - Tate Gallery (75 photographs) (Box 84)
                - Milwaukee (5 photographs) (Box 84)
                - New York (7 photographs) (Box 84)
                - Washington, D.C. (14 photographs) (Box 84)
        - U – V (11 photographs) (Box 85)
          - W (318 photographs) (Box 85)
          - Wa (18 photographs) (Box 85)
          - We-Wi (23 photographs) (Box 85)
          - Wo-Wy (12 photographs) (Box 85)
          - Wadsworth, Edward, 1889-1949 (6 photographs) (Box 85)
          - Walker, Robert, 1607-1658/60 (5 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Walton, Henry, 1746-1813 (4 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Ward, James, 1769-1859 (9 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Waterhouse, John William, 1849-1917 (21 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Watts, George F., 1817-1904 (39 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Wheatley, Francis, 1747-180 (9 photographs) (Box 86)